Guide to the Actors' Fund of America Records WAG.036
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Missing Title
I, Minutes, 1880-1991.
II, Annual Reports, 1882-2000.
III, General Files, 1881-2005.
IV, Actors Work Program, 1986-1999.
V, Fundraising Activities, 1886-2002.
VI, Catholic Actors Guild Records, 1924-1980.
VII, Family Papers, 1903-1974.
VIII, Society of Stage Directors and Choreographers Records, 1959-1980.
IX, Oversized Items, 1891-1965.
X, Scrapbooks and Unprocessed Material, 1900-1973, 2000s.
Series XI, Aldrich Family Papers, circa 1850-1940.
Series XII, Archived Website
Related Material at the Tamiment Library/Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Actors' Fund Photographs (PHOTOS 240)
Actors' Equity Association Records (WAG 11)
Associated Actors and Artistes of America Records (WAG 110)
Theater Authority Records (WAG 183)
Appraisal
Books from the 2014 donation already held by the Tamiment Library were not retained.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Due to the fragile nature of the fifteen scrapbooks covering the years 1900-1961, researchers must use the microfilmed version; microfilm call number is Film R-7822.
Custodial History
The archived website was migrated from the California Digital Library's Web Archiving Service to the Internet Archive's Archive-It Service in November 2015. The link to California Digital Library was removed in October 2017.
Theater |z United States.; Theater -- New York (State) -- New York.; New York (N.Y.); Clippings (information artifacts); Actors -- United States.; Benefit Performances.; Entertainers |z United States |x Economic Conditions.; Actors |z United States |x Economic conditions.; Bazaars (Charities) |z New York (State) |z New York.; Annual reports.; Correspondence.; Los Angeles (Calif.); Microfilms.; Ledgers (account books).; Fliers (printed matter); Financial records; International labor activities.; Newsletters.; Minutes (administrative records); Entertainers -- United States.; Press releases.; Scrapbooks.; Sound recordings.; Actors' Fund of America -- History; Abbott, George, 1887-1995; Dewhurst, Colleen; Cooley, Hollis.; Catholic Actors Guild of America; Broadway Cares/Equity Fights AIDS (Organization); Hayes, Helen, 1900-1993; Frohman, Daniel, 1851-1940; Fiske, Harrison Grey, 1861-1942; Dillon, Tom.; Keeler, Ruby.; Lester, Edwin.; Henderson, Florence.; Hughes, Bernard.; Mostel, Zero, 1915-1977; Munsell, Warren P.; Logan, Nedda Harrigan; McGlinn, Frank; Rathbone, Ouida Bergere, 1887-1974; Reynolds, Debbie.; Nichols, Mike.; Rathbone, Basil, 1892-1967.; Simon, Neil.; Society of Stage Directors and Choreographers (U.S.); Shaw, Rosette.; Simon, Louis.; Swayd, Lester.; Sponder, Wanda.; Williams, Percy.; Tompkins, Don.; Wolfington, Iggie; Actors' Fund Home (Englewood, N.J.); Actors' Equity Association; Actors' Fund of America; Engelman, David
- Series I: Minutes, 1880-2006; 184461
  - Minutes: Annual Meeting, 1880-1929; 184527 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Minutes: Annual Meeting, 1977-1978; 184526 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Minutes: Annual Meeting, 1985-1986; 184525 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Minutes: Annual Meeting, 1989; 184524 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Minutes: Annual Meeting, 1991; 184523 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Minutes: Board of Directors of the Actors' Fund Home, 1957-1966; 184522 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Minutes: Board of Directors of the Actors' Fund Home, 1967-1974; 184521 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Minutes: Board of Directors of the Actors' Fund Home, 1976-1985; 184520 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1887-May 1895; 184519 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, Jul 1895-1917; 184518 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1918-1919; 184517 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1920-1921; 184516 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1922-1923; 184515 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1924-1925; 184514 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1926-1927; 184513 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1928-1929; 184512 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1930-1931; 184511 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1932-1933; 184510 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1934-1935; 184509 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1936-1937; 184508 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1938-1939; 184507 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1940-1941; 184506 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1942-1943; 184505 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1944-1945; 184504 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1946-1947; 184503 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1948-1949; 184502 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1950-1951; 184501 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1952; 184500 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1953-1954; 184499 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1955-1957; 184498 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1958-1959; 184497 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1960; 184496 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1961; 184495 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1962; 184494 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1963; 184493 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1964; 184492 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1965; 184491 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1966; 184490 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1967; 184489 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1968; 184488 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1969; 184487 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1970; 184486 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1971; 184485 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1972; 184484 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1973; 184483 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1974; 184482 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1975; 184481 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1976; 184480 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, Jan 1978; 184479 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, Feb 1978; 184478 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, Mar 1978; 184477 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, Apr 1978; 184476 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, Oct 1978; 184475 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, Nov 1978; 184474 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, Dec 1978; 184473 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, Jan 1979; 184472 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, Feb 1979; 184471 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, Mar 1979; 184470 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, Apr 1979; 184469 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, Oct 1979; 184468 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, Nov 1979; 184467 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, Dec 1979; 184466 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, Apr 1991; 184465 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1981-1990; 2015.024; 591810 (Box 53, Folder 1-2)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1990-1992; 2015.024; 591811 (Box 53, Folder 3-4)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1991-1992; 2015.024; 591812 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 2004-2006; 2015.024; 591813 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Minutes: Board of Trustees, Special Meeting, 1977-1978; 184464 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Minutes: Executive Committee, 1882-May 1889; 184463 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Minutes: Executive Committee, Jun 1889-1894; 184462 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Series II: Annual Reports, 1882-2012; 184362
  - Annual Reports (bound), 1882-1893; 184460 (Box 4)
  - Annual Reports (bound), 1894-1902; 184459 (Box 4)
  - Annual Reports (bound), 1903-1912; 184458 (Box 4)
  - Annual Reports (bound), 1913-1922; 184457 (Box 4)
  - Annual Reports (bound), 1923-1931; 184456 (Box 4)
  - Annual Reports (bound), 1931-1941; 184455 (Box 4)
  - Annual Reports (bound), 1942-1952; 184454 (Box 4)
  - Annual Reports (bound), 1953-1960; 184453 (Box 4)
  - Annual Reports (bound), 1961-1967; 184452 (Box 4)
  - Annual Reports (bound), 1968-1975; 184451 (Box 4)
  - Annual Reports, 1902; 184450 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1903; 184449 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Annual Reports, 1904; 184448 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Annual Reports, 1905; 184447 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Annual Reports, 1906; 184446 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Annual Reports, 1907; 184445 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Annual Reports, 1908; 184444 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Annual Reports, 1909; 184443 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Annual Reports, 1910; 184442 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1911; 184441 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Annual Reports, 1912; 184440 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Annual Reports, 1914; 184439 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Annual Reports, 1915; 184438 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Annual Reports, 1916; 184437 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Annual Reports, 1917; 184436 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Annual Reports, 1918; 184435 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Annual Reports, 1919; 184434 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Annual Reports, 1920; 184433 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Annual Reports, 1921; 184432 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Annual Reports, 1922; 184431 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Annual Reports, 1924; 184430 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Annual Reports, 1925; 184429 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Annual Reports, 1926; 184428 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Annual Reports, 1927; 184427 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Annual Reports, 1928; 184426 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Annual Reports, 1929; 184425 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Annual Reports, 1930; 184424 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Annual Reports, 1931; 184423 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Annual Reports, 1932; 184422 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Annual Reports, 1933; 184421 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Annual Reports, 1934; 184420 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Annual Reports, 1935; 184419 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Annual Reports, 1936; 184418 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Annual Reports, 1937; 184417 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Annual Reports, 1938; 184416 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Annual Reports, 1943; 184415 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Annual Reports, 1944; 184414 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Annual Reports, 1945; 184413 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Annual Reports, 1946; 184412 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Annual Reports, 1947; 184411 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Annual Reports, 1949; 184410 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Annual Reports, 1950; 184409 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Annual Reports, 1951; 184408 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Annual Reports, 1952; 184407 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Annual Reports, 1953; 184406 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Annual Reports, 1954; 184405 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Annual Reports, 1955; 184404 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Annual Reports, 1956; 184403 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Annual Reports, 1957; 184402 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Annual Reports, 1958; 184401 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Annual Reports, 1959; 184400 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Annual Reports, 1960; 184399 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Annual Reports, 1962; 184398 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Annual Reports, 1963; 184397 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Annual Reports, 1964; 184396 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1965; 184395 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Annual Reports, 1966; 184394 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Annual Reports, 1967; 184393 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Annual Reports, 1968; 184392 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Annual Reports, 1969; 184391 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Annual Reports, 1970; 184390 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Annual Reports, 1971; 184389 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Annual Reports, 1972; 184388 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1973; 184387 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Annual Reports, 1974; 184386 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Annual Reports, 1976; 184385 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Annual Reports, 1977; 184384 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Annual Reports, 1978; 184383 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Annual Reports, 1979; 184382 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Annual Reports, 1980; 184381 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Annual Reports, 1981; 184380 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Annual Reports, 1982; 184379 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Annual Reports, 1983; 184378 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Annual Reports, 1984; 184377 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Annual Reports, 1985; 184376 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Annual Reports, 1986; 184375 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Annual Reports, 1987; 184374 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Annual Reports, 1988; 184373 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Annual Reports, 1989; 184372 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Annual Reports, May 1989-Apr 1990; 184371 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Annual Reports, May 1990-Apr 1992; 184370 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Annual Reports, 1992; 184369 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Annual Reports, 1993; 184368 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Annual Reports, 1994; 184367 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Annual Reports, 1995; 184366 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Annual Reports, 1996; 184365 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Annual Reports, 1997; 184364 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Annual Reports, 1998-2000; 184363 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Annual Reports, 2004-2012; 585782 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Marquee and Annual Reports, 2011-2017 (Box 55, Folder 1-3)
- Series III: General Files, 1881-2013; 184172
  - Abbott, George: 100th Birthday Celebration, 1987; 184361 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Actor Participation in Performances, Lists of, undated, 1946, 1950; 184360 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Actors' Equity Association, 1963, 1966, 1976; 184359 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Actors' Equity Association, 1988; 184358 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Actors' Fund Appreciation Month, 1988-1989; 452438 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Actors' Fund Art Gallery, undated, 1984; 184357 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Actors' Fund Home, 1925-1972; 184356 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Actors' Fund Home: Board Correspondence, 1980-1986; 2015.024; 591814 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Actors' Fund Home: Christmas Party, 1984; 184355 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Actors' Fund Home: Clippings, undated, 1912-1949; 184354 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Actors' Fund Home: Clippings, 1951-1959; 184353 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Actors' Fund Home: Clippings, 1961-1969; 184352 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Actors' Fund Home: Clippings, 1970-1983, 1996-1997; 184351 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Actors' Fund Home: Clippings, 1980-1984; 2015.024; 591815 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Actors' Fund Home: Edwin Forrest Day, 1991; 184350 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Actors' Fund Home: Edwin Forrest Day, 1993; 184349 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Actors' Fund Home: Edwin Forrest Home, 1885, 1931; 184348 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Actors' Fund Home: Extended Care Facility, 1987; 184347 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Actors' Fund Home: Financial Ledger, 1959-1962; 184346 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Actors' Fund Home: Groundbreaking Ceremony, 1984; 184345 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Actors' Fund Home: Guests, 1936, 1967, 1981-1985; 184344 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Actors' Fund Home: Plaques, 1991; 184343 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Actors' Fund Home: Press, undated, 1972, 1985; 184342 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Actors' Fund Home: The Spotlight (newsletter), 1992-1993; 184341 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - AIDS Project Volunteer Program, 1989; 184340 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - AIDS Quilt, 1992; 184339 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - AIDS Training and Education Project (ATEP), 2004; 184338 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA), 1986-1987; 184337 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Anniversaries, 1957, 1963, 1972; 184336 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Anniversaries: 100th, Articles for, undated, 1981; 184335 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Anniversaries: Clippings, 1972; 184334 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Annual and Annual Associate Member Dues Book, 1965-1982; 184333 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Annual Meeting: Clippings and Flyers, 1930-1931, 1949, 1950; 184332 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Avis, 1987-1988; 184331 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Awards and Certificates, 1989, 1992-1999; 184330 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Award of Merit, 1952-1965; 184329 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Blood Banks, undated; 184328 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Blood Drive, 1970-1982; 184327 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Broadway Cares, 1988-1990; 184326 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Broadway Cares/Equity Fights AIDS, 1991; 184325 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Brochure, 1988; 184324 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Buck, George: Portrait, 1941; 452432 (Box 7, Folder 38a)
  - By-Laws, 1912, 1955; 184323 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - By-Laws: Amendments, 1991; 184322 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Campaign Materials: "Responding to to Essential and Evloving Needs", April 2010; 2015.024; 591816 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Career Transition for Dancers Program, 1987; 184321 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Cobb, Irvin S.: "The Deadheads of the Lord", 1933; 184320 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Commemorative Stamp Campaign, 1978-1981; 184319 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Commonwealth Fund, 1996; 184318 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Cooley, Hollis E: Clippings, Membership Cards, and Memorabilia, 1917-1919; 184317 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Cooley, Hollis E.: Telegram Recommendations for Panama-Pacific International Exposition, 1913-1914; 184316 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, undated; 184315 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1899, 1928-1937; 184314 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1940-1949; 184313 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1950-1979; 184312 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Curtain Call (Actors' Fund Documentary), 2001; 184311 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Dewhurst, Colleen, 1991; 184310 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Dillon, Tom: Memorial, 2005; 184309 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Donor Lists and Box Number Confirmations, undated; 184308 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Edison, Thomas: Note to Actors' Fund, 1919; 184307 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Edwin Forrest Society: Scripts, 1997-2004; 184306 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Episcopal Actors' Guild of America, 1953, 1989; 184305 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Equity Fights AIDS, 1991; 184304 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Equity News: Press Releases and Correspondence, 1979; 184303 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Equity, "Official Organ of the Actors' Equity Association and Chorus Equity Association", 1928; 184302 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Event Programs, 2014-2016 (Box 55, Folder 8-11)
  - Evergreens Cemetery, Actors' Fund Plot Books (3 separate volumes), 1885-1965; 184301 (Box 8, Folder 20, Box 54)
  - Fair Housing Council of Northern New Jersey, 1987; 184300 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Father's Day Brunch (Harrigan Award to Lloyd Bridges), Jun 1989; 184299 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Fendi, 1987; 184298 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Finances, 1962; 184297 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Finances, 1963; 184296 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Finances, 1964; 184295 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Finances, 1965; 184294 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Finances, 1966; 184293 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Finances, 1967; 184292 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Finances, 1968; 184291 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Finances, 1969; 184290 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Finances, 1970; 184289 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Finances, 1971; 184288 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Finances, 1972; 184287 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Finances, 1973; 184286 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Finances, 1974; 184285 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Finances, 1975; 184284 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Finances, 1976; 184283 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Finances: Advertising, undated, 1935-1941; 184282 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Finances: Application for Charity Rate in Advertising and Tax Status, 1942-1948; 184281 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Finances: Benefit Department: Statements, 1931-1944; 184280 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Finances: Chemical Bank Ledger and Checks (incoming and outgoing), 1887-1897; 184279 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Finances: Equity Members Aided, undated; 184278 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Finances: Fundraising, undated, 1928, 1933-1938; 184277 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Finances: Fundraising, 1939-1951; 184276 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Finances: History, 1970, 1981-1982, 1991; 184275 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Finances: Ledgers, 1884-1891; 184274 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Finances: Receipts, 1934-1950; 184273 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Founder's Day Picnic, 1989; 184272 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Frohman, Daniel, 1920-1940; 184271 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - FUNDamentally Yours (Actors' Fund newsletter), 1956; 184270 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Guest Books, 1961, 1978, 1986; 184269 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Guiterman, Arthur: "A Health to All Players" (Poem Written for Actors' Fund), 1937; 184268 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Harris, Henry B. (Casualty of the Titanic), 1912; 184267 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Hayes, Helen, 1976, 1980; 184266 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Hayes, Helen: Dorothy Patten "Love of Chattanooga Awards", 1986; 184265 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Hayes, Helen: National Artist Awards, Gala Program, 1976; 184264 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Health Fair, 1986; 184263 (Box 9, Folder 4, Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Historical Society of Pennsylvania: Edwin Forrest Collection, 1988; 184262 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - History (Actors' Fund): Effrat, John, "Broadway Angels", undated; 184261 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - History (Actors' Fund): General, undated, 1923-1940, 1977; 184260 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - History (Actors' Fund): Hewitt, Alan, "Places, Please, for the Next 100 Years", undated; 184259 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - History (Actors' Fund): Simon, Louis, A History of the Actors' Fund of America: Correspondence, 1968-1975, 1981; 184258 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - History (Actors' Fund): Simon, Louis, A History of the Actors' Fund of America: Publicity and Reviews, 1972-1973; 184257 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Hughes, Bernard: Tribute, 2002; 184256 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Hundley, John Walker: Poem for Warren P. Munsell, 1974; 184255 (Box 9, Folder 11a)
  - Lester, Edwin, 1944, 1958, 1963-1964; 184254 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Licenses for Sunday Performance, 1935-1972; 184253 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Life Members, 1968, 1978; 184252 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Logan, Nedda Harrington, 1989; 184251 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Luncheons, undated, 1955-1971, 1981; 184250 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Lyceum Theatre, 1973; 184249 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Manhattan Plaza Apartment Program, 1988; 184248 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Marquee (newsletter), 1996-1998; 184247 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Marquee (newsletter), 1999-2004; 184246 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Marquee (newsletter), 2003-2009; 585783 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Marquee (newsletter), 2010-2013; 585784 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - McGlinn, Frank (Trustee), 1979-1997; 184245 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Membership Advertisement, 1975-1976; 184244 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Membership Advertisement, 1982,1991, 2000; 184243 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - "Milton on the Actors": Poem, 1937; 184242 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Monument, Kensico Cemetery, 1940-1941; 184241 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Mostel, Zero, 1978; 184240 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Munsell, Warren P., 1956-1980; 184239 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - National Executive Service Corps: Report on the Actors' Fund, 1991; 184238 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - New Jersey, Works Progress Administration: Theatre Project, 1937-1937; 184237 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - New York City Opera: Costume Donation, 1991; 184236 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Officers, undated, 1905; 184235 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Officers and Staff: Clippings, 1912-1982; 184234 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Palmer, A. M., undated, 1903; 184233 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Pamphlets and Flyers, undated, 1926-1967; 184232 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Playbills (souvenir), 1939, 1942, 1945; 184231 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Playbills (souvenir), 1955-1959, 1984-1989; 184230 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Playbills (souvenir, signed), 1988; 184229 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Press Releases, undated, 1933-1968; 184228 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Press Releases, 1970; 184227 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Press Releases, 1971; 184226 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Press Releases, 1972; 184225 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Press Releases, 1973; 184224 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Press Releases, 1974; 184223 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Press Releases, 1975; 184222 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Press Releases, 1976; 184221 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Press Releases, 1979; 184220 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Press Releases, 1989; 184219 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Program Inserts, undated, 1959-1979; 184218 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Programs, Invitations, and Ephemera, 2014-2017 (Box 55, Folder 4-7)
  - Programs (souvenir), undated, 1893-1922; 184217 (Box 10, Folder 15)